(Sheldon:)Oh, yes. But there's usually planning,
courtship, advance notice.
You know, last time, I was able to book
a cruise to the Arctic to see a solar eclipse.
Wait, wait. You had to leave the state
because your roommate was having sex?
(Sheldon:)I didn't have to.
The dates just happened to coincide.
(Penny:)So do you know who's in there?
(Sheldon:)Well, there's Leonard.
And he's either with Leslie Winkle
or a 1930s gangster.
Hmm. Good for him.
(Penny:)Good for Leonard.
(Penny:)Okay. Night.
No, don't. Wait, hold on.
(Leonard(entering):)- What's the matter?
- I don't know what the protocol is here.
Do I stay? Do I leave?
(Sheldon:)Do I wait to greet them
with a refreshing beverage?
(Penny:)Gee, Sheldon,
you're asking the wrong girl.
(Penny:)I'm usually on the other side
of the tie.